<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learning Adventures</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/</link><description>Recent content on Learning Adventures</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 15:16:38 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://law.aritao.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CloudFlare Pages: Deploy Awesome Static Sites, Quickly.</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/seven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 15:16:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/seven/</guid><description>Cloudflare Pages. Another awesome way to deploy a site. I was pleasantly surprised to see how user-friendly Cloudflare Pages is. As someone doing coding and development as a new hobby, it&amp;rsquo;s refreshing to use intuitive tools and an uncluttered interface.
The steps I followed to deploy were:
Create a repository on github.com. Create the Hugo site locally Initialize a git repository in the local Hugo site work directory, and commit it to the remote repository, main branch.</description></item><item><title>Little Things Make Me Happy</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/six/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 18:32:07 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/six/</guid><description>Typography, for instance Typography is the visual component of the written word.
-Matthew Butterick
It feels so good to read text visualized and displayed through good typography.
Books, magazines, websites, apps, user interfaces come alive with the right typefaces. I find Butterick&amp;rsquo;s Practical Typography and Typography for Lawyers very helpful.
I have three guidelines when choosing typefaces / fonts for my work:
They should be easy to read on screen and on paper.</description></item><item><title>What Matters</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/five/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 19:45:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/five/</guid><description>Everyday Treasures by Law Aritao
I would like to create something new every day. I would like to take a picture, tell a story, share an idea, or illustrate something.
I would like to say a kind word, hold my wife&amp;rsquo;s hand, hug my children, tell them I love them.
I would like eat something tasty, walk a few miles, listen to music.
I would like to make a wish, say a prayer, think kind thoughts for others.</description></item><item><title>Reflecting on the Why (of this Site)</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/four/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 21:31:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/four/</guid><description>by Law Aritao
Reflections on Why I want to explore why I am doing this blog and why I consider Hugo and Github pages a great choice.
Why Hugo and Github Pages? In the past twelve months, I explored Wordpress, Ghost, Wix, Wordpress/Ghost on various platforms: Google Cloud, Amazon Web Services, Azure, Linode, Digital Ocean, and Vultr. I also tried creating a static site and hosting it on Amazon Amplify.</description></item><item><title>Beautiful Markdown</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/three/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 16:46:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/three/</guid><description>by Law Aritao
Beautiful Markdown Hugo, my preferred site generator, supports Markdown, a beautiful markup language that&amp;rsquo;s been around since 2004. I love Markdown. It is simple. It is beautiful. It is intuitive (once you get the hang of some fundamentals).
It&amp;rsquo;s gotten so bad that I now have several Markdown editors on my devices, and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind more. I use Caret, Inkdrop, Nota, and SimpleNote. Caret is nice because it is available on both Windows and MacOs, and it is gorgeous.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/contact/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 20:36:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/contact/</guid><description>Reach out IG: coffeeandthis
Twitter: law_aritao
Github: lawrenceaph</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 20:35:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/about/</guid><description>Adventures in Learning</description></item><item><title>A Learning Adventure - Part Two</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/two/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 07:23:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/two/</guid><description>by Law Aritao
I walk farther down the path of Hugo and Github Pages. So much fun.
Photo credit: Thomas Willmott on unsplash.
Deeper Down the Rabbit Hole As I worked on site content and structure, I switched to this theme for its design and overall quality. Reading the theme&amp;rsquo;s documentation gave me some additional lessons in the way Hugo creates the static output (Hugo&amp;rsquo;s lookup order). The relatively painless switch in themes gave me a greater appreciation for Hugo&amp;rsquo;s design.</description></item><item><title>A Learning Adventure via Github + Hugo</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 07:23:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/one/</guid><description>by Law Aritao
Wonderful Github Somtimes I wish I could just learn by osmosis. With Github, I found the next best thing.
Photo credit: Dmitry Ratushny on unsplash
Down the Rabbit Hole I recently figured out how to use Github pages to host a Hugo-created blog site (got interested because of this. As I was learning the method, I got hooked on the beauty of Github. After tinkering and understanding Github a little bit more, I have fallen in love with it.</description></item></channel></rss>