<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hugo on Learning Adventures</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/categories/hugo/</link><description>Recent content in hugo on Learning Adventures</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 21:31:45 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://law.aritao.dev/categories/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on the Why (of this Site)</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/four/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 21:31:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/four/</guid><description>by Law Aritao
Reflections on Why I want to explore why I am doing this blog and why I consider Hugo and Github pages ideal. I would like to stop and think about that, because I explored numerous self-publishing tools, but didn&amp;rsquo;t feel content unti I discovered Github pages and Hugo. What was it about the Hugo and Github Pages combination that caused me to stop searching for a platform and start generating content steadily?</description></item><item><title>Beautiful Markdown</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/three/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 16:46:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/three/</guid><description>by Law Aritao
Beautiful Markdown An upside to learning how to use the static site generator Hugo is that I&amp;rsquo;m also able to develop fluency in Markdown, the beautiful markup language Hugo uses for its content posts. I love Markdown. It is simple. It is beautiful. It is intuitive (once you get the hang of some fundamentals).
It&amp;rsquo;s gotten so bad that I now have several Markdown editors on my devices, and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind more.</description></item><item><title>A Learning Adventure via Github + Hugo</title><link>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 07:23:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://law.aritao.dev/blog/one/</guid><description>by Law Aritao
Wonderful Github Somtimes I wish I could just learn by osmosis. With Github, I found the next best thing.
Photo credit: Dmitry Ratushny on unsplash
Down the Rabbit Hole I recently figured out how to use Github pages to host a Hugo-created blog site (got interested because of this. As I was learning the method, I got hooked on the beauty of Github. After tinkering and understanding Github a little bit more, I have fallen in love with it.</description></item></channel></rss>